We Will Rock You
摇滚万岁
乐队：Queen
压制:随Feng
Buddy you're a boy make a big noise
伙计你是一个小男孩 大声嚷嚷的
Playing in the street gonna be a big man some day
在街头鬼混 希望有一天能成为大人物
You got mud on your face
你脸上流着鲜血
You big disgrace
颜面尽失
Kicking your can all over the place
把铁罐到处踢来踢去
Singing
唱吧
We will we will rock you
我们要让你摇滚起来
Buddy you're a young man hard man
伙计 你是一个年轻人 是一条硬汉
Shouting in the street gonna take on the world some day
在街头叫嚣 总有一天要接管这个世界
You got blood on your face
你脸上流着鲜血
You big disgrace
颜面尽失
Waving your banner all over the place
到处挥舞着旗帜
We will we will rock you
我们要让你摇滚起来
Singing
唱吧
We will we will rock you
我们要让你摇滚起来
Buddy you're an old man poor man
伙计 你老了 穷光蛋一个
Pleading with your eyes gonna make you some peace some day
眼里祈求着宽恕 总有一天可以使你得到平静
You got mud on your face
你搞得灰头土脸
You big disgrace
狼狈至极
Somebody better put you back into your place
最好有人能把你赶回老家去
We will we will rock you
我们要让你摇滚起来
Singing
唱吧
We will we will rock you
我们要让你摇滚起来
Everybody
大家一起来
We will we will rock you
我们要让你摇滚起来
Alright
好极了
压制:随Feng